Friends, good evening, brother, today
in the market, absolutely nothing will happen, if it does
not break today, it will break tomorrow, and the big
move, whose expectations, the hopes that were there
today, will not happen today but will happen tomorrow, there is no
doubt in it brother, not much time is going to pass, the
market is about to show a move,
friends, we will discuss in which direction it is going to show a move, we will
try to guide the stock,
welcome to your own channel, okay,
my name is Tribhuvan in Money, let's
start the discussion, first of all, the most
important market i.e. Nifty, friends,
almost nothing has happened in Nifty, if you say,
Nifty is stuck in a range,
where is the tree, now first of all,
where is the six for a big move, it is around 12, it is
not much above, it is around 12,
India team is around 12, next now see what is the
scenario of the bull market here, when and
how can we rally, see
first, if you want to rally, a small
rally, not a big one, if you want to do a small rally, then an
easy level is
visible here, see which level is that,
friends, 630  If
Nifty crosses above 1730 around then you
can look for a target of 50 points with a stop loss of 20 points and a stop loss of 20 points because tomorrow is the expiry so you can
make good money in 50 points, remember the
stop loss is 20 points, that is
your stock will be around 610,
around 17610 and when to go bullish is when
Nifty crosses above 630, above 17630,
above 6:30 and your first target is this
level, this level of yours is around
67580, around 675 680 is going to be
your first target and
if Nifty crosses that level friends then
you
can take approximately 70 points there and then you can take the target, you can
play for a bigger target,
so the butter will be that if you are playing in two lots,
which I always say, but you should
play only in 50
points, but I was the first one to allow booking at 50 points  For the
future, your target for that is
around 17000 750, it
is around 17750, for the second lot, the
target edge remembers you because the
next resistance is around that, Nifty is
expiring, moving up and down by 100-150 points is
not a big deal, it keeps you in mind,
especially today when nothing has happened, it is possible that
tomorrow Nifty can show a big move, there is
no doubt in it, now see friends,
what is the idea in the big T, if Nifty goes below ₹590,
below 17590, then T has to be done
and you can move with the target, the first
support is
around 17500, around 17500, the first
support can be your target, when to go
below 17590 1790, what is the first target, around 17500
and here the second target is, if
suppose the level of 500 is broken, then
your next target is from 17430  7430 is
the thing you keep in mind for bullishness
friends, we use only 5 minute chart,
you know
RM pattern you can remember, you can bullish in W,
you can bullish on 5
minute chart
everyone you can take a target of 70 points in
Nifty, let's go to Nifty Bank,
son brother today Nifty is also a father,
when to bullish in Nifty Bank,
friends, at least above 200, above 200, when
42000 you 25 comes out, remember
42000 you 25,
when Bank Nifty comes out, only then we will
bullish and the first target can be around 42000 450,
42450, your first target in Bank Nifty,
when to hit, when to hit,
we can hit below 4250 4250 and
our first target is on this time friends,
what is it going to be,
your first target is 41000
₹750
41750 which is going to be your target in the market,
here also you
can follow the RM pattern, stop loss of 60 points,
target of 200 + coins, you can go to Yes Bank, first of all
in the stock brother,
where is the support of Yes Bank, the support is around 15 15
and if the train moves then how far
can it go, where is the resistance around 18.5 18,
such a long and huge fall brother, the
resistance is around 11:30, the
award is around 100050, let's go to PNB,
friends, there is resistance in PNB around 52
and the support of PNB is around 46, let's go to
Maruti Suzuki,
Maruti is a good stock with resistance around 9000 9000, you
can pick it up if it falls below,
Maruti's first support is around 8300,
Maruti Suzuki, remember in this I
told you friends, after talking to a
financial advisor for video education and information purpose
I'll reduce it a little more carefully,
thanks.